https://www.healtheconomics.com/privacy-policy

Value Communication
Free Marketing Consultation!
HE Institute
You are here: Home / Privacy Policy.
HealthEconomics.Com recognizes the importance of protecting the personal privacy of its customers, potential customers and website visitors. This internet privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the information that may be collected through our website, the choices you can make about our use of your personal information and how we protect your personal information.
At any time, you have the right to review, modify, or delete any information you may have provided to HealthEconomics.Com. We will, upon your request, export and provide this data to you. Please submit your request to privacy@healtheconomics.com.
Scope and Terms Used
This Privacy Policy applies only to website operated by or on behalf of HealthEconomics.Com (the “Site”). Unless otherwise indicated, all references to “HealthEconomics.Com” “we” or “our” in this Privacy Policy shall mean HealthEconomics.Com, LLC. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any offline data collection or practices of HealthEconomics.Com, LLC.
The Site may contain links to the websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of those websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of each website you visit.
As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information that may be used to identify a specific individual, or that is about an identifiable individual, such as includes Name, Job Title, Company, City, State, Country, email address. “Aggregate information” refers to combined demographic information which has been derived from personal information but which cannot be used to identify any individual or that is not about an identifiable individual.
Information We Collect and How We Use It
You can visit the Site and learn about our services and programs without providing personal information. We do not collect any personal information on the Site unless you provide it voluntarily. We use Hatchbuck and Amazon SES for our email distribution services. You should visit their website for their privacy statement, terms and conditions of use and other pertinent information. From time to time, HealthEconomics.Com may run surveys for our internal use to create reports, and gather user feedback on products and services. We may also contract to run surveys for third parties who wish to understand more about their audience. You always have the choice to participate anonymously, or not at all. We use SurveyMonkey to field these surveys. Please visit their website to learn more about their privacy policies, and terms of use.
In addition to our General Uses listed below, we use the personal information you provide only for purposes consistent with the reason you provide it, such as:
Information Requests: We may ask you to provide personal information in order to allow us to respond to your requests for information or other requests made over the Site. If provided, the exhibitors will have access to certain information, including your name, job title, company, city, state, and email information. You always have the option to choose not to participate.
Newsletter: On the newsletter section of the Site, you may provide us with your e-mail address in order to subscribe for our newsletter, which contains the latest information on news, jobs, resources in HEOR, Market Access and Real-world Evidence, as well as our products, events and our other offerings.
Contests and Surveys: In addition to your name, address and other identifying information, we may ask you to provide other information about your household and interests if you choose to participate in our contests or surveys. You can always choose not to participate.
Non-personal Information: Using Google Analytics, we collect non-personal information such as your Internet browser type, operating system, geographic location, and the IP address of the website from which you are linked to the Site. We use this information to help us tailor our Site in a manner to better match your computer settings, interests and preferences. If you wish to find out more about the information provided through Google Analytics, you may do so by visiting requesting this information from Google.
General Uses: We may also use your personal information internally to customize your experience with our company and our Site, help us develop new products and services, verify your identity, collect debts owed to us, or investigate or settle inquiries or disputes, and for other legally required or permissible purposes.
What Are Cookies and How Does We Use Them?
Cookies are small text files stored by your browser that allow us to learn more information about your visit or use of the Site. We may use cookies to remember your personal information, including your registration information, and to deliver personalized and relevant information specific to your needs. We may also use cookies to track patterns on the Site to help us improve visitor or customer experience.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies. The following resources are provided to educate visitors on how to manage cookies on popular browsers:
Google Chrome
Microsoft Edge
Mozilla Firefox
Microsoft Internet Explorer
Opera
Apple Safari
To find information relating to other browsers, visit the browser developer’s website.
We use Google Analytics to collect non-personal data in order to better understand visitor traffic on our site and which content provides the most value. Information gathered might include your gender, age, geographic location, browser type, and device type. Google offers tools to allow visitors to opt out of tracking, available here:
http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Click here to see a list of the cookies served by HealthEconomics.Com. This list is subject to change.
To find out more about our cookie policy, click here.
Your Choices In How We Use Your Personal Information
While we may contact you with offers and information concerning our products, services or promotions, you always have the choice not to receive such items by using the unsubscribe links provided at the bottom of these emails. You may also submit a request to remove your personal information from our site at privacy@healtheconomics.com.
You may contact us with any questions or concerns you may have about our privacy practices, including requests to update or correct your personal information.
Our Sharing of Your Information
HealthEconomics.Com provides certain customer contact data (such as customers’ names, company, job titles, addresses, and e-mail addresses) to third parties who wish to promote relevant products, services and other opportunities which may be of interest to you. If you do not want HealthEconomics.Com to make your contact information available to third parties for marketing purposes, contact us by mail at HealthEconomics.Com, 1327 Walnut Street, Jacksonville, FL 32206, USA.
HealthEconomics.Com may also share your personal information collected on the Site with third parties as necessary or appropriate to (i) process or fulfill your order, (ii) respond to your requests or answer your inquiries, (iii) enter you in contests, sweepstakes or other promotional activities upon your request, or (iv) comply with any applicable law, court order or other judicial process or as otherwise required or permitted by law. In addition, in the event of a corporate transaction such as a sale, merger or reorganization involving HealthEconomics.Com, personal information may be disclosed or transferred to the purchaser. We may collect and share aggregate website statistical information (such as sales, traffic patterns or related information) with third parties. No such shared statistics will contain any personally identifying user information.
We may occasionally hire contractors to provide certain services on its behalf, including information processing and storage or the management of contests, sweepstakes and surveys. These contractors are required to maintain the confidentiality of information they receive from us and are restricted from using the information for any purposes other than those authorized by HealthEconomics.Com.
We Protect Your Information
When you submit sensitive information via our Site, such as credit card information, that information is subject secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption technology. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information during transmission, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us.
Submissions
Suggestions, materials or other intellectual property sent or transmitted to us via our Site is governed by the separate terms applicable to such materials identified at the time of submission (if any). If no such terms are identified, all such items shall be deemed to be non-confidential, and we shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such items and shall be free to use and distribute them to others without limitation, including, but not limited to developing and marketing products incorporating them.
Children’s Privacy
Our Site is not intended for use by children under 17. We ask that children under the age of 17 do not use our Site and do not submit any personal information to us.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, you may contact us at privacy@healtheconomics.com or by mail to HealthEconomics.Com, 1327 Walnut, Jacksonville, FL 32206, Attn: Privacy Department.
Your Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy
By using our Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy, and you agree to adhere to the terms and conditions posted on the Site under “Legal notice.” If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not submit any personal information to us through our Site.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so you should review it frequently. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post such changes here and/or on our Site.
View All JobsPost a JobView Current NewsletterSubscribe to Newsletters
Conference of the Week:
Link of the Week:
Job of the Week:
Webinar of the Week:
White Papers
Whitepaper: The Role of Centralized Care Management in Value-based Care2017 In-Depth Outlook on Oncology ReportValue-Based Healthcare: Making it HappenValue-Based Contracting for Biopharmaceuticals Moves ForwardICER Releases White Paper on Gene Therapy
Syndicated Reports
HTA in Europe: Key Success Factors for Positive HTA RecommendationsPaying for Digital Health: Payer InsightsBenchmarking Pharma’s MSL CapabilitiesBiosimilars: US Payer PerspectivesKAM Metrics: Driving Efficiency, Measuring Success
News
Jobs
HE Jobs Portal
View all Jobs
Post a Job
The HEOR & RWE Marketplace
Visit the Market Place
On-demand Webinar
Free Marketing Consultation!
